Narrator: Stressed Sally
Speaker 1: have a shower
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: have a coffee
Narrator: 13
Speaker 1: do the housework
Narrator: 8
Speaker 1: start work at 8.30
Narrator: 10
Speaker 1: finish work at 6.30
Narrator: 3
Speaker 1: get dressed
Narrator: 1
Speaker 1: wake up at 7 o’clock
Narrator: 9
Speaker 1: have lunch at work
Narrator: 11
Speaker 1: go shopping
Narrator: 16
Speaker 1: go to bed
Narrator: 14
Speaker 1: have pizza for dinner
Narrator: 12
Speaker 1: get home late
Narrator: 6
Speaker 1: go to work by bus
Narrator: 4
Speaker 1: put on make-up
Narrator: 15
Speaker 1: check emails
Narrator: 7
Speaker 1: get to work
Narrator: Relaxed Robbie
Speaker 2: go to Italian classes
Narrator: 17
Speaker 2: get up at 8 o’clock
Narrator: 20
Speaker 2: have breakfast
Narrator: 18
Speaker 2: have a shave
Narrator: 22
Speaker 2: go home early
Narrator: 21
Speaker 2: walk to work
Narrator: 26
Speaker 2: relax
Narrator: 19
Speaker 2: take the dog for a walk
Narrator: 28
Speaker 2: sleep for eight hours
Narrator: 25
Speaker 2: make dinner
Narrator: 27
Speaker 2: have a bath
Narrator: 24
Speaker 2: see friends